=A Taste of First Love=
= طعم الحب الأول =
=Episode 7=
= الحلقة 7 =
Ren Mingyuan.
رن مينجيوان.
You are in luck!
كنت في الحظ!
You sealed the deal with Chicheng.
لقد أبرمت الصفقة مع تشيتشنغ.
I worked hard for this.
لقد عملت بجد من أجل هذا.
For sure, you are getting promoted.
بالتأكيد ، يتم ترقيتك.
By the way,
على فكرة،
when are you marrying your girlfriend?
متى تتزوج صديقتك؟
Marry?
الزواج؟
How can I possibly marry her?
كيف يمكنني الزواج منها؟
If she wasn't the owner of Sun Group's daughter,
إذا لم تكن صاحبة ابنة صن جروب ،
I would never date her.
لن اواعدها ابدا
Didn't the Sun Group declare bankruptcy long ago?
ألم تعلن صن جروب إفلاسها منذ فترة طويلة؟
A starved camel is bigger than a horse.
الجمل الجائع أكبر من الحصان.
I was planning to make use of her resources
كنت أخطط للاستفادة من مواردها
but she turns out to be a burden.
لكنها تبين أنها عبء.
Brothers are my hands and feet,
يا اخوتي يدي وقدمي
while women are as clothing.
بينما النساء كملابس.
Cheers!
هتافات!
Weiyi.
ويي.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Let's talk after we go back home, okay?
لنتحدث بعد أن نعود للمنزل ، حسنًا؟
Guys,
رفاق،
I'm the "princess" of the Sun Group,
أنا "أميرة" مجموعة صن ،
I'm also the useless burden
أنا أيضا العبء غير المجدي
with poor family background as Mr. Ren said.
مع خلفية عائلية فقيرة كما قال السيد رن.
It seems like he's about to get rich
يبدو أنه على وشك أن يصبح ثريًا
and planning to get rid of me.
ويخطط للتخلص مني.
I'm so lucky.
أنا محظوظ جدا.
But
ولكن
thank you
شكرا لك
for showing me his true intention.
لتظهر لي نيته الحقيقية.
However,
لكن،
you might look like a gentleman on the outside
قد تبدو كرجل نبيل من الخارج
but you talk about women like they are a piece of clothing.
لكنك تتحدث عن النساء وكأنهن قطعة ملابس.
What a self-centered and arrogant man
يا له من رجل أناني ومتغطرس
are you.
أنت.
Are you really breaking up with me?
هل حقا تنفصل عني؟
The way you treated me in front of my colleagues
الطريقة التي عاملتني بها أمام زملائي
was such a humiliation.
كان هذا إذلال.
You don't intend to apologize to me
أنت لا تنوي الاعتذار لي
and now you are chasing me out?
والآن أنت تطاردني؟
Why shouldn't I kick you out?
لماذا لا أطردك؟
Ren Mingyuan.
رن مينجيوان.
Now I have seen through you.
الآن لقد رأيت من خلالك.
You are just a selfish
أنت مجرد أنانية
and hypocritical scumbag.
والنفاق النفاق.
Sun Weiyi.
صن ويي.
I admit.
أعترف.
I was drunk and said something I shouldn't have.
كنت في حالة سكر وقلت شيئًا لا يجب أن أفعله.
But look at yourself now.
لكن انظر إلى نفسك الآن.
With your conditions,
مع ظروفك ،
do you think you deserve me?
هل تعتقد أنك تستحقني؟
Let's break up then.
دعونا نفترق إذن.
Don't waste your time on me.
لا تضيعوا وقتكم علي.
You don't have to pretend to care for me
ليس عليك التظاهر بأنك تهتم بي
but in fact, you are just a stingy person.
لكن في الحقيقة أنت مجرد شخص بخيل.
Fine.
بخير.
Sun Weiyi.
صن ويي.
Sure, let's break up.
بالتأكيد ، دعونا نفترق.
But first,
لكن اولا،
let's sum up the time and money
دعونا نلخص الوقت والمال
that I've spent on you these years.
التي قضيتها عليك هذه السنوات.
LV Speedy bag, 6,000 yuan.
حقيبة LV سبيدي ، 6000 يوان.
You buy me a fake one.
تشتري لي واحدة مزيفة.
It is worth only 300 yuan.
تبلغ قيمته 300 يوان فقط.
You brought me to some roadside stall
لقد أحضرتني إلى كشك على جانب الطريق
on my last birthday.
في عيد ميلاد الماضي.
The store used mutton that was pumped with water.
كان المتجر يستخدم لحم ضأن تم ضخه بالماء.
I ended up with diarrhea and spent 2,000 yuan in hospital.
انتهى بي الأمر بالإسهال وقضيت 2000 يوان في المستشفى.
Now, let's calculate how much I've spent on you.
الآن ، دعنا نحسب كم أنفقت عليك.
Your watches and shoes
ساعاتك وأحذيتك
that I bought are international brands.
التي اشتريتها هي علامات تجارية عالمية.
They cost at least 10,000 yuan.
تكلفوا ما لا يقل عن 10000 يوان.
You just had a haircut in the salon
لقد كان لديك للتو قصة شعر في الصالون
and paid for it with my VIP card.
ودفعت ثمنها ببطاقة VIP الخاصة بي.
Let's round it up.
دعونا نقربها.
50,000 yuan.
50000 يوان.
Fine.
بخير.
I was blinded.
كنت أعمى.
Do you still think of yourself as a high-born?
هل مازلت تعتبر نفسك من كبار السن؟
(When a woman said she doesn't want to fall in love anymore,)
(عندما قالت امرأة إنها لا تريد الوقوع في الحب بعد الآن ،)
(do I still have a chance?)
(هل مازال لدي فرصة؟)
(Why do women like a man who's far inferior to them?)
(لماذا تحب النساء رجلاً أدنى منهن بكثير؟)
(What if the woman doesn't like me back?)
(ماذا لو لم تعجبني المرأة؟)
Mr. Bai.
السيد باي.
The contract with Chicheng Group
العقد المبرم مع مجموعة تشيتشنغ
is ready.
جاهز.
Mr. Liang asked
سأل السيد ليانغ
if you are free tonight?
إذا كنت متفرغ الليلة؟
He wanted to ask you out for a drink.
أراد أن يطلب منك مشروبًا.
I'm busy.
أنا مشغول.
Well,
نحن سوف،
Mr. Liang said
قال السيد ليانغ
both of you are single
كلاكما عازب
so you need some opportunities
لذلك أنت بحاجة إلى بعض الفرص
to meet some girls.
للقاء بعض الفتيات.
Tonight,
الليلة،
he asked his friend to invite some professors,
طلب من صديقه دعوة بعض الأساتذة ،
stewardesses, and doctors over.
مضيفات ، والأطباء أكثر.
Every one of them is very good-looking.
كل واحد منهم حسن المظهر للغاية.
I've told you I don't have time.
لقد أخبرتك أنه ليس لدي وقت.
I'm busy.
أنا مشغول.
Tell him, leave me alone
قل له ، دعني وشأني
except for business.
باستثناء الأعمال.
Boss,
رئيس،
Miss Sun broke up
انفصلت الآنسة صن
with her boyfriend not long ago.
مع صديقها منذ وقت ليس ببعيد.
Why didn't you tell her
لماذا لم تخبرها
what kind of person Ren Mingyuan is?
أي نوع من الأشخاص هو Ren Mingyuan؟
She wouldn't believe whatever I say about Ren Mingyuan.
لم تصدق ما أقوله عن رين مينجيوان She wouldn't believe what I say about Ren Mingyuan.
Oh,
أوه،
how about you and your girlfriend?
ماذا عنك أنت وصديقتك؟
We are getting married.
نحن سنتزوج.
I'm serious about her.
أنا جاد بشأنها.
We broke up years ago
لقد انفصلنا منذ سنوات
but we got back together recently.
لكننا عدنا معًا مؤخرًا.
You...
أنت...
What's the trick?
ما هي خدعة؟
You've come to the right person.
لقد أتيت إلى الشخص المناسب.
The trick is to ignore her rejection and never give up.
الحيلة هي تجاهل رفضها وعدم الاستسلام أبدًا.
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
But I'm doing that already, aren't I?
لكنني أفعل ذلك بالفعل ، أليس كذلك؟